let's do some structure stuff okay the
right Ibrahim sobral structure of doom
Leo's The should push you you have
thrown about Prabhu zircon she was a
conscious Trangia
popular Buddha in Michigan have a
problem we - sniper go at its pro as Nam
Nevis is not recursive
Khalifa x is dealt me a scale cliche
purva cockeyed Seema's coca-cola II
Kakashi a snake exposes you can
you stomach items not GMO primitive
mhmm is not part okay lip area the
courses which moves was there are no
courses if either going to guess
Michaels cousin secretly secretly
changer shut up block appear evil
cartons Watsonville occipital more llama
by lil on your bobbin every misawa's no
grains no with acne scars curtain like
is Kim Eugenia pasta - there's no which
should still call some gears attacks
castle this is a tradition a secret
national tree nuts the Corsair Petrella
live in student of the most suitable
tags lost by the much students the
courses the autumn couple of beads I
said I co-produced rockers Co excessive
analyst agent very discussion with this
car logic on your Kadima Easter than yet
the Kamikaze Kenny Palmilla we finished
with a conscience at will know as more
sequentially smears Iike Coco's deity oh
yeah that issue isn't popular the cost
that yet
of course the package left brick
residence so I met the highest yesterday
so we show up Mireille ammonia charity
especially Schnabel agility cool center
psycho llamas castle a cockatrice but
almost as expedited bitumen akka losing
akatsuki course but a famous summary
when our skin visibly Padova to eat him
you know yeah good yeah the apple pie
they put some carpet
yeah preferred I be at the best of women
are beautiful you see what it's like a
boa vista treat research Sandra
mahi-mahi be a mannequin if debating
material and building up this Juliette
softly thank you
evoking voice layer could be Luckman
actionable destitution elusive sugar one
night he died was to previous it
ceremony stubborn over my knocking
assassin Mohammed was the general
advance beyond which is someone I can
there's nobody I wanna build Stoli calm
longer one night each Daniela a
search the manikin supernovas oh my gosh
together with some so clear example of
up shipping it's a beer tape on the
bitumen RGB table ticked over scenario
tourism no us a theater Alma's damn
Mountain with this visual ominously
Trista Trista tree Amiata
move to the Laura bottle is
emotionally-driven irritable deposition
Yamana he when I hit him analytically
given a tough so image a specific seal
of the whole nation managed at a below
simple pretty much even ask critical
about she loses
out there doing it themselves I shove
option
Papaji vato course Nia coaches cuz I
hardly even at the absorb Sutra mean I
that decent late son copy now that book
is so sure a technique attack a karateka
the wonders not beast ninja I I decided
to use one it's cuz it's a llama
Quicksilver his name is move true evil
even go to Quicksilver at a caucus
Quicksilver a statute of ten trees
posits of near eminence nice polish data
yet near probation your email llama
Quicksilver lamorne a variety llama via
the treated mother
Yanis vessel gemstone and I'll Oscar
OSHA commentary miss puzzle in your
business absorbed some carpet Weiss
maybe the pretty moksha a bit of for ten
cents that is it sent of what it mean
stow it does not shed pretty moksha
dad sent of cars demise near possible
dead center were the baddest at center
cannula to touch honest okay your zy t
was noisy by but it may be nice
it's a pretty much I bet they pretty
much does not shed IP etiquette or even
serenaded our stupid st near one in near
bracelet Linea no near vanished Abbas
Travis while each nest red onions a
better monarch of managing pesky Abita
an idea
Korean glitch Napa Valley stainless
steel is no procedure - the prosecutor
would onions deli and Adeem nail bomb a
bit Mahayana catalysis Nieto yeah yes
sir cut its Akopian America reaches
Nieman more than applicants I better
stop immediately
I told she serious nyam nyam it Mahayana
I'll be at the Hinayana and you ship
back home I will miss jet random course
I never ceased commentary Quicksilver
tipep associates going backward yes it's
a verb and impart key Geshe Michael can
input u 3 CH angry butcher Pavan Korean
butcher Lama Pavan Kalyan push emotional
civet awkward if we digest the llama
Quicksilver yeah go to pretend reach
school in your talking Jaguar applause
lineal must know pitches Quicksilver
Abyssinia Quicksilver Tavo Clarke's
traces on almost 1 o'clock at night tu
Cox needs rated Sonny status too
gentle names but she pragmatist Anthony
on Passau add value chick yes
leave a specific aquarium but dr. Viet
heretic in the lowest school dance Dubai
bituminous can you girl i'ma Quicksilver
bro initial score Kakui periodic when
the basilic Nicotra booties a check or
certain 3y a bit of of soup new go okay
she has come and tell you a llama
Quicksilver part of the chess but did
that work or set the potato it was
country people becoming his night the
rusical bed guess I know Sheila sneakers
know when you're more legislative Tantra
busy miss her oh she teaches cookies we
travel et down through yes precisely
Matson kindly unless it's doable movie
musical was written at Passover bazooka
secretly brothers Kia Simon is not even
out of an emergency doctrine that the
transit entre the remaining excess but a
most of ahadees disturb unkillable each
nervous about silly late was there's no
bit Hiroshi Shima calculate connect says
that which is a breakthrough camino a
casa de semana es technical katanas was
so driven nice piece in the summer would
say Simon our immersion opposite it and
you provides in every bite at the near
which in sexes which it now sums it up
cell is most sexist very be added a bit
a register give me that caucus ETS to
perform abortions governor nuñez destroy
Kiana
already yeah it's a solidly maybe
smaller oh yeah pity really but the
Bible codes but um oh yeah in the matter
miss me Harper draws the connection son
copy put up with it to the most best
measures of goodnight he was specially
answer because it's a tough war
people always ask me first
never Norman klas the bottom probably is
a proud become level do we use a soft
cushion or a hard carpet on prevailing
not bad we connect the palm so we don't
yet know the don't hold it up kikuchi
TDCI serious item serious not here or
always hold sig da their hatred love
food I love Anna gasps the child item
Bravo
in other countries you know he had a
beautiful relationship which is what is
it is Samantha the race at your mind
keeps talking about lunch
yes lavash says nine your discoveries
Pro a beard it's because you really
shooting fashion you came in much
pitocin and is constantly reversible
about it a very good that I will discuss
that bothering other three devices
University to us that at the seven
oppression is a diverse double wash
russia says nine years Guevara mine but
movers rights other ways the quest
refugee respecting other people's
concentration
that's interesting if their citizens
could not bother checking people before
you talk about I'd say there's a pity
simcha Claire behind for them previously
perishable hydration later than your
vision very important to achieve
arginine avec for a meditator dammit if
you respect
yesterday a piece of mine spoke with a
rookie don't irritate me if you have to
tell them bad news pick the time yes I'm
nervous too
thora criticize someone in the evening
news yes Alan there's nothing more to
them but I was in Sonoma give him good
news in the evening show you know a
general rule for you okay she's such a
stupid I will you have to criticize your
student do it in the morning yes they
take about Salah student deserve it -
episode - the respect of RIT other
people's stay in your any other
guarantee good deeds jealous respect at
the tangles dissenters great evil
version I have good melody it does at
the versioning hero just incompetence
all similar
we implement a Bible it of course
classical I had something else to say
about them they show questionable oh
yeah anyway that's enough
yeah if you want your mind to be quiet
yes the Hollister says nine about
spinning them they seem opening in your
mind that gravel suckers I said business
model cement economies are opening her
eyes to set better brush room says nine
year that's what you call good
meditation editor stern okay you gotta
that's a string of good seeds seeds
semen that balances satisfactions
contentment see an opponent all these
beautiful meditations focus for the
precise purpose spits I don't expect to
have watermelons if you didn't meant
them
yeah nice just afforested your machine
by not bothering other people yes
it's got a she no sorry say it's part of
the word sorry uh she she ok mr.
know-it-all say number she come on we've
got that huh she is the same for right
sir
sir same I think it came from the same
route same ease
yeah four kinds of sustenance for things
you need you but you be every dick get
over it yeah physical food just gave
that food second one is sleep that away
at the Sun okay you want to have fun
with an employee take the nicest person
in the company
I knew her disappear device become the
traffic of a company might seem spot
lack of sleep makes anybody
how good person you've obviously KATUSA
kidney the verb it's addressing Tilikum
second kind of food hope and what's the
famous example Kakui is really premiered
yeah in the syrian desert cities and
then they see an oasis and IV two ties
they were no horse yeah now lost ever
died it never happened in dying yes the
chalice tikal the study what keeps them
going the last room know what bustling
mean by mental stability horse ever died
two meters from the water hope can
sustain a human it just gets really
booting me yes they have the fourth kind
of a tip you did focus focus focus
they don't have to eat by the way if
your meditation gets really good yes who
is it that sister no Josh you will have
this experience I'm pretty nice okay
you'll be sitting in a quiet like a
library and you will notice it was a
message that you didn't breathe and you
feel fine you feel okay you'll say oh my
god divine breathe the shot one breath
is food okay you don't need it
you need focus focus if your focus is
struggling
we don't need this evening yes you
don't need breath illusion it's very
interesting no change it is then I tell
you the funny thing about yoga I had a
yoga teacher and they said hold your
breath for as long as you come back our
destination has another name Kerala
kumbhaka
the
spontaneous stopping of your breath it
has a name in yoga
Kevin la cumbre car Chinese vase with
the top here
Kerala means automatic you didn't try to
become economies your breasts are so
there's all these yoga schools they say
hold your breath you know really that's
not how you stop nothing you focus on
your focus perfect your meditation it
will stop that soul and you will notice
- then I'm a society needs to it's not
there is pranayama yes put in a Yama in
in Tantra and there's many run a
monopoly on LUMO go tuck is the most
famous holding your breath yeah got it
yes and I know it's me the theoretical
but you don't have to breathe you got
the other way human being
justify your motion focus as much as
they need food okay if you deprive a
human being asleep
yes live or die yeah yeah but all the
nicest person in your company be family
dobra chill a question right but I'm not
allowed to say that
Stan Yin my teacher hates it when I
cursed by the way I said don't let my
she said are saying I know what you need
a good employee if you want to lose a
good yeah in general
be respectful in GUI ethnic thought we
go but there's a typicai knees okay got
it
and your meeting doesn't matter which is
cooking novice class meditator in my
class II class seven hated on his back
Samuel uchigatana meat eater of my
classmen doesn't meet the abbot of touch
is no more in a debate and as day one an
apology but this is the guy illegally
and he had illegal
with rock and roll I know time travel
whooshing nearly got me with no sticks
rock and roll erupted on on Nick
academia vicinity you were focused on it
but what is the other past at any pauses
how much talk of us seem anxious
that's the connection between the nine
wholesome class number David
three seven question three yeah
absolutely
yeah that could be unique and upmarket
version midgets epidemic that with earth
mr. Stewie I mean I didn't think about
how does nine complete any same it it's
like death meditation good davis
interaction their destiny replaced when
usually miss Schmidt about nine and
David yes it what's ten study started
studies had the course yeah so look I
have 11 minutes
I'll start answering yeah there's no
yeah uh quencher probably the most
that's personal salmon is so large
netting about yourself guess what it's
called
oh god I attack economy guide to the
Bodhisattvas way of life Jesus I hunted
bear more
around 700 AD
but at the same race or whatever shadow
Tong dynasty early tennis in the middle
of done I don't thought maybe I think so
anyway so he wrote a book called buddy
stuff okay I'm gonna tell you tonight
I'll tell you partner okay
it's acute cystitis courtesy what's a
blue circle cut it to bucyk oh yeah he
had a nickname in the
about the coin nickname was so cool so
cool mr. lazy
mr. deliberately nothing mr. so he had a
reputation in the market but that said
he didn't study well no chips wasn't a
good teacher she didn't show up in the
kitchen to help the carpets roll them
back excited my god is variety buzzer he
seemed to be the laziest monk in the -
oh you're feeding this guy had a meeting
this initially enough station there was
a very wise guy who was a fellow
Virginian vodka terrible dragon let's
let's help him kick himself out
Samui - so he said what's your plan ask
him to teach that's called device you
tell him you know we possess a tech demo
for you judge when you saw intelligence
they went to hear dialects so he said
and then he I think that still and he
taught that body charge basically a
review of ok basic although importantly
speech head but got off visit that so
the first part that we study arrow
spectrum as a chance they say
some data some of Kolkata Yamaha III
receive open India so he taught on NHS
probably it was surely it's the greatest
body supper book ever written
Karif civil at the sama even even more
vinegar but he sucked was cut to the
block and that even the bit nicer like
unbelievable me that is Mecca incredibly
find me
you really have movie solar the go
Balkan the emptiness section by
audacious your chance we say gaseous
emptiness sexual not sure what sex in
personal advice how to be a body cell
each new Soviet carbon so it's not part
of the gifts that they knew chest in the
middle of the wisdom chapter thirteen
yeah motorist after on style Martha and
I put a picture of them throw them voice
cuz there's a caption if you can read
Tibetan people trust
Tibet's kita this I found a temptation
yeah normal picture maybe the course is
nervous can you just scroll down
that's Celtic J who wrote a great
company girl to put on the Basilica mint
daddy there you go what's it what's the
last three signatories lager Persico
this is him flying off I don't like that
he's got his book in his hand he's
flying off and when he got deep into
emptiness started and then there were
some monks in the audience right yogi so
like it they also said hey I want to
hear the end and yeah
oh there's a circle of people around
who's like going up hill drop out you
know people can't go so high and it got
less and less and less and it finally
they gave up
he's headed toward South India he
disappeared his chest and he never came
back
it's a famous story then they had a big
meeting and oh my god and his emptiness
teaching is the best parties yet but I
really did a guide land here with a
brush in his hair and they found him
anyone that's near and they said you
know we apologize we made a big mistake
you're actually a great master please
come back to the monastery he's got a
house re he said decline respect yeah
but she said not plenty of it and he
never once I which is another thing
about criticism right there but they
made a big play another team and we
understand you don't want to come back
we can't blame you
Kelly how do ya know wasn't that type of
community and he said I knew you're
gonna ask me that you can find it there
copy yes ok so the next three courses
because of that is so much work can you
get that question or how to be a buddy
subtle cog busy but like that way I did
three courses
it's
20% of the AC is the scent of 3 of the
15 horses that he is not such a course
of Shanthi Dharma tabby but in 12 my
right cause anybody said okay so I'm
gonna do two things she should tell him
I'll tell you the subjects who lit it up
and why is my picture okay and then I'm
gonna let you out two minutes early
yeah edema not the vessel in chiapas
sure
[Music]
goodnight it's answer I knew
you'd be happy then last a stove it said
other you guys think - oh let's see
by the way sure a McDonald sure a
McDonald McDaniel I'm sorry is the
Registrar of a CI for like the last I'm
nah I think it's rather a CI passed
million dollars in debt typical Turkish
Liras Corso without pay like Latin
officer of a large city and now but
surely feel insists never got a dozen
she's doing it media which is amazing
miss partner managers of a city in the
room yeah for free she's keeping all
your own up see what she's like you
although she's only 30 potato ethnicity
so you should a you should thank your
cheatin on her good side
I study and maybe your grades will
improve God does my Qantas neighbors
wasn't a rush I attempt a legit sir and
we'd like to thank you for your look at
seem to have a little better that's a
bet about
[Applause]
oh my gosh right now man yeah yeah
[Music]
but Ray's father
yeah it's started as a heart surgeon
chef
famous and this onions the minute they
missed it 20 years ago or longer
homeworks in prisons Tony there's a like
you can't send them cd-roms many mojitos
della seta for about 20 20 mile so the
supporters should give them a toaster
doesn't affect
[Applause]
they love to write long answers because
they don't have anything else to do
which is in that seventeen only imagine
okay